Okay so let's look more carefully at this model for
好的 现在让我们更加仔细的来观察这个模型
accepting rejecting students.
这个模型接受或者拒绝学生
Let's say we have a student four who got nine on the test but
比如说有一个学生四 他在这次测试中得到了9分
one on their grades.
但是他的成绩是一
That student gets accepted according to our model,
根据我们的模型 这个学生应该被接受
since they are over here on top of the line.
因为他在这条线的最上面
But that seems wrong,
但是这似乎不对
since the student got very low grades shouldn't get accepted.
因为这个学生有一个非常低的成绩 这不应该被接受
So, maybe it's too simplistic to think that this data can be separated by just
所以也许仅仅想要用一条线来区分这里的数据
a line, right?
太简单了 对吗？
Maybe the real data should look more like this where these students who got
也许真实的数据应该那些得到
a low test score or low grades still did not get accepted.
低的测试分或者是低的成绩的都不应该被接受
So it seems that a line won't cut it anymore.
所以似乎这条线已经不能分离这些点了
What's the next thing after a line?
用一条线之后的下一个能做的是什么呢？
Maybe a circle?
也许是一个圆？
A circle could work.
一个圆可能会有效果
Maybe two lines?
也许两条线？
That could work too.
那也许也能有效
Let's go with that.
让我们来处理这个
let's go with two lines.
让我们试一下两条线
And how do we find these two lines, again we can do it using
我们能够怎么找到这两条线呢 再一次我们可以做这个
gradient descent to minimize a similar log lost function as before.
通过梯度下降来最小化一个和之前相似的对数损失函数
This is called a neural network,
这被称为神经网络
now the question is why is this called a neural network.
现在这个问题是为什么这被称为神经网络
Well let's say we're working in a very slow computer which can
比如说我们在一台非常慢的电脑上面工作
only do one thing at a time.
一段时间仅仅能够处理一件事
So it's not easy to just ask,
所以非常不容易来问
is this point in the area bounded by these two lines?
这个区域的点被两条线区分开了吗？
We have to split it into separate questions.
我们必须要把这个分成两个单独的问题
The first question is, is the point over the blue line?
第一个问题是 这个点在这条蓝线之上吗？
Let's answer that question based on the four black points in the graph.
让我们基于这个图上的4个黑点来回答这个问题
We can see that for this four points.
对于这四个点 我们能够看出
The answers are Yes, Yes, No, and No.
这个答案是对的 对的 错的 错的
The second question is, is the point over the orange line?
第二个问题是 这个点在这条橘色的线上面吗
And we can see that for the four points the answers are No, Yes, No, and Yes.
对于这4个点 我们能够看出这个答案是 不对 对 不对 对
Now, the third question will just take the answers from the previous two, and
现在 第三个问题就是把前两个的答案取出来
combine them.
组合他们
So the third question is, are the answers to questions 1 and 2, both yes?
那么第三个问题 第一个问题和第二个问题的答案都是对吗？
And we can see that for these four points,
对于这四个点 我们能够看出
the answers are no, yes, no, and yes.
答案是不对 对 不对 对
So they are all no, except for the one that is in the green area.
所以除了这个在绿色区域的这个点 他们都是不对
Now let's craft each question as a small note.
现在让我们取出每个问题作为一个小的节点
The first question is, is the point over the blue line?
第一个问题是 这个点在蓝色的线之上吗？
We have a node with the area and two input nodes.
这个区域我们有一个节点和两个输入节点
The test score and the grades.
测试得分和成绩
For example we have a student where the test score is one and
例如我们有一个学生 测试成绩是1
the grades at eight.
成绩是8
The node plots the point and checks that the point is on top of the black line.
这个节点画出这个点 检查这个点是不是在这条黑线上面
And returns the answer, yes or no.
返回这个答案 对或是错
The second question is similar, we input test grades and the corresponding node.
第二个问题是相似的 我们输入一个测试分数和成绩进入相应的节点
We'll plot the point, and return a yes or
我们将会画出这个点 返回正确还是错误
a no depending on the point being on top of the orange line or not.
依赖于这个点在橙色线的上面还是没有
Now, the third question.
现在 第三个问题
Are the answers to questions one and two both yes?
问题1和问题2的答案都是对吗？
We'll just take as inputs the answers to the two previous questions, and
我们将会把前面两个问题的答案作为输入
return a yes if the two answers are yes and a no otherwise.
如果这两个答案都对的 就返回对的 否则就返回错
This is known in logic as the and operator.
这个在逻辑运算中称为"和"运算符
Now, this is where the magic happens.
现在 这就是魔法发生的地方
If we join the nodes for these three questions, then we get a neural network.
如果我们把这三个问题合在这个节点中 我们就得到了一个神经网络
And if we clean it up a bit, we have the following.
如果我们简化一下 就得到了下面的东西
The first column is where we input testing grades.
第一列使我们输入测试和成绩的地方
And the second column is where we checked that the point with coordinates
第二列是我们检查这些和测试成绩有关的
corresponding to the test and the grades is on top of each one of the lines.
坐标点是否在每条线的上面
And the third layer in which we look at the answers from the previous layers and
第三层我们看看前面的层的答案
join them with the and operator.
用"和"运算符把他们合在一起
So this is how our neural network will look.
那么这就是我们的神经网络的样子
Now you may be thinking something's a little suspicious here.
现在你也许在想这些事有点让人怀疑
The first two nos look like they take values and
前面两个输出的错看起来就像他们取值
check if the corresponding point is on top or below a certain line.
然后检查相关的点在特定的直线上还是下
Whereas the third node just takes yes or no and returns yes or no.
因此第三层仅仅是输入对或者错 然后返回对和错
Is it possible to see the third node as one of the first two?
有可能把第三层的节点看作是前面两层节点中的一个吗？
And the answer is yes.
答案是可以
So let's look at the and operator in more detail.
那么 让我们来更进一步看看"和"运算符
Let's actually make a little table of what goes in, and what goes out.
我们实际做一个表格 表格上有输入和输出
So with the and operator if we put a yes and a yes, we get a yes.
那么使用"和"运算符 如果我们用对和对作为输入 我们得到一个对
If we input a yes and a no, we get a no.
如果我们输入对和不对 我们得到一个不对
If we input a no and a yes, we get a no.
如果我们输入一个不对和对 我们得到一个不对
And finally if we input a no and a no, we get a no.
最后如果我们输入一个不对和不对 我们得到不对
Now, we can think of a yes as a one and a no as a zero.
现在 我们能够想像对作为1 不对作为0
In that case, our table turns into this other one.
在这种情况下 我们的表格变成了另外一个
And now, look at this operator in which we enter value zero and one and check if
现在 我们输入0和1进入这个运算符 检查一下
the corresponding point with those coordinates is over or above the line.
相对应的点的坐标在线的上方还是下方
If we look at the points for coordinates (1,1), we get that this
如果我们看看这个点(1,1) 我们会得到
point is over the line on the green or positive region, so we get a one.
点在绿色的线上面或者是在正的区域 所以我们得到1
Now if we look at the points with coordinates (1,0),
现在如果我们看看(1,0)这个点
we see that it's under the line on the red or negative region.
我们会发现它在红色的线下面或者是说在负的区域
So we get a 0.
所以我们得到0
Similarly for the point with coordinates (0, 1),
对于(0, 1)坐标的点是相似的
this point is under the line, so we get a 0.
这个点在直线下方 我们得到0
And finally, the point with coordinate (0, 0) is under the line too.
最后(0, 0)坐标的点也在这条直线下面
So the answer is 0 again.
所以答案再一次是0
So this is how our final neural network looks.
那么这就是我们的最终的神经网络的样子
On the left, we have what's called the input layer, where in this case,
左边 我们叫做输入层
we're inputting the test scores and the grades.
我们输入测试分数和成绩
Here we have a case where the test score is 1 and the grades are 8.
这里我们有一个情况 测试分数是1 成绩是8
Then this goes through a middle layer,
然后这通过了中间层
called the hidden layer, which will help us with our computations.
这被称为隐藏层 会帮助我们计算
So in here we can see that the 1 and the 8 go become the point with
所以在这里我们能够看到1和8一起变成了一个点
coordinates 1,8 on the two graphs in the next layer.
有着坐标1和8 在下一层的两幅图中
In the top node the point (1,8) is on the green or positive region so
在上面的节点 (1,8) 在绿色或者是说在正的区域
the top node emits a yes.
所以这个点输出一个对
In the bottom node the point (1,8) from the red or negative region, so
在下面的点中(1,8)在红色或者是在负的区域
the bottom node emits a no.
所以底下的节点输出一个错
Now we remember that a yes is represented by a 1 and
现在我们记得对可以被1表示
a no is represented by a 0.
不对可以被0表示
Now the next layer, called the output layer,
现在下一层被称为输出层
takes the values coming out of the middle layer, mainly the 1 and the 0.
取值来自于中间层 主要是1和0
And it locates the point with coordinates (1, 0).
它定位在了坐标是(1, 0)这个点
This point is in the red or negative region of the final node, so
这个点是在最后节点的红色或者是说负的区域
the output here is a no.
所以输出是一个错
Does the neural network has received this inputs,
神经网络已经收到了这个输入
the values test equals 1, and grades equals 8, and it has outputted a no.
值为1的测试分数和值为8的成绩 它输出了一个错
This is a simple neural network, but you can see how adding more nodes in
这是一个简单的神经网络 但是你能够看出如何增加更多的节点在
the middle or even more layers of nodes can help us map more complex
中间甚至是更多的节点层可以帮助我们在平面上映射更加复杂
areas in the plane or even in three dimensions or higher dimensional spaces.
的区域甚至在三维空间或者是更高维的空间
Neural networks are a very powerful machine learning algorithm used
神经网络是非常强的机器学习算法
in most state of the art projects such as facial recognition,
其被使用在大多数人工项目中比如面部识别
voice recognition, playing chess, and self-driving cars.
语音识别 下棋和自动驾驶
And we call it a neural network because these nodes resemble
我们称它为神经网络是因为这些节点像
neurons in the brain.
大脑里面的神经元
And neurons will take as input, the output of other neurons in the form of
神经元将会把输入和其他神经元的输出以一种
nervous impulses and decide to fire a nervous impulse or not.
神经脉冲的形势 决定是否激活这个神经脉冲
In our case the neuron takes as input the output of other neurons in the form
在我们的情况中 神经元把输入和其他神经元的输出以
of numbers.
数字的形势
And decides to return a 1 or a 0.
决定返回一个0或者是一个1